Guide to the Arnie Goldwag Brooklyn Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) collection ARC.002
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 2: Books, 1943-1993; 6.5 Linear feet
  - Stetson, Erlene (ed.), Black Sister, 1981 (Box 17, Item 15)
  - Stone, I.F., In A Time of Torment, 1967 (Box 17, Item 16)
  - Stringfellow, William, My People is the Enemy, 1966 (Box 16, Item 17)
  - Summers, Clyde W. and Robert J. Rabin, The Rights of Union Members, 1979 (Box 16, Item 18)
  - Sussman, Alan and Martin Guggenheim, The Rights of Parents, 1980 (Box 16, Item 19)
  - Sutherland, Elizabeth (ed.), Letters from Mississippi, 1966 (Box 16, Item 20)
  - Suttles, Gerald D., The Social Order of the Slum, 1973 (Box 17, Item 17)
  - Tanner, Leslie B. (ed.), Voices from Women's Liberation, 1971 (Box 19, Item 18)
  - Taylor, Telford, Grand Inquest, 1961 (Box 19, Item 19)
  - Thomas, Piri, Down These Mean Streets, 1968 (Box 16, Item 20)
  - Toffler, Alvin, Future Shock, 1970 (Box 16, Item 21)
  - Ture, Kwane (Stokely Carmichael) and Charles V. Hamilton, Black Power: The Politics of Liberation, 1992 (Box 20, Item 23)
  - Walker, Daniel, Rights in Conflict, 1968 (Box 16, Item 24)
  - Weinberg, Meyer (ed.), W.E.B. Du Bois: A Reader, 1970 (Box 17, Item 18)
  - Whalen, Richard J., A City Destroying Itself: An Angry View of New York, 1965 (Box 18, Item 19)
  - Wilcox, Preston (ed.), White Is, 1970 (Box 16, Item 20)
  - Wilson, Edmund, The Cold War and the Income Tax: A Protest, 1964 (Box 19, Item 21)
  - Youth of the Rural Organizing and Cultural Center, Minds Stayed on Freedom, 1991 (Box 20, Item 24)